{
    "subject": "resource/Subhumans_(Canadian_band)",
    "predicate": "ontology/recordLabel",
    "object": "resource/Quintessence_Records",
    "human_readable": "Subhumans (Canadian band) was released by Quintessence Records.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.978125274181366,
            "question": "Is Subhumans (Canadian band) affiliated with Quintessence Records?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9468649625778198,
            "question": "What Canadian band's music was released by Quintessence Records?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9228290915489197,
            "question": "What is the name of the Canadian band that had its music released by Quintessence Records?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9057098031044006,
            "question": "What is the name of the Canadian band that released music through Quintessence Records?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8858332633972168,
            "question": "Name a band that released music on Quintessence Records."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8853511214256287,
            "question": "Which record label released music by Subhumans (Canadian band)?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7956282496452332,
            "question": "Which record label issued Subhumans (Canadian band)'s music?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7618191838264465,
            "question": "Who are the musicians behind the album released by Quintessence Records?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7589959502220154,
            "question": "Who was responsible for releasing music by Subhumans (Canadian band)?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6794021129608154,
            "question": "Can you name a band associated with Quintessence Records?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Subhumans (Canadian band) was released by Quintessence Records.",
            "html": "dbpedia_1696_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Who was responsible for releasing music by Subhumans (Canadian band)?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1696_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Who are the musicians behind the album released by Quintessence Records?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1696_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Which record label issued Subhumans (Canadian band)'s music?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1696_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1696_10.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1696_11.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1696_21.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1696_29.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1696_34.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1696_35.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1696_50.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1696_6.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1696_71.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1696_93.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'no'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'no'}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"no\"\n}\n```\n\nExplanation: The documents provided do not mention anything about the band Subhumans being released by Quintessence Records. The information in the documents is related to details about the punk rock band Subhumans, their members, and history but does not include any reference to a record label named Quintessence Records."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"no\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 0,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Least Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {
        "mistral": {
            "reason": "There is no evidence or information provided in the context that suggests the Subhumans (Canadian band) was released by Quintessence Records.",
            "category": 4
        },
        "gemma2": {
            "reason": "There is no mention of Quintessence Records being associated with the Subhumans (Canadian band) in any of the provided text.",
            "category": 4
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "reason": "Quintessence was not a record label, but rather a British counterculture band that existed from 1969-1973. There is no evidence to suggest that they were ever associated with the Subhumans as a record label.",
            "category": 4
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "reason": "The context information clearly states that Subhumans was a Canadian punk rock band formed in Vancouver, British Columbia, and provides details about their members and history. There is no mention of Subhumans being released by Quintessence Records or any connection to the British counterculture band Quintessence mentioned in another context.",
            "category": 4
        }
    }
}